All releases will be done on Curse.com AND WoWInterface.com so grab it from wherever you prefer.

Main support site:
https://muffinmangames.com


*For Cooldown counts please use Omni Cooldown Count
*For skinning install the Masque addon

To Do:
 - Pets (Favourite, and All).
 - Toybox (Favourite and All)

Changes:
v6.0.2.16 --Pending
 - Hearth: Added Wormhole Centrifuge
 - Fun: Added Walter, Blingtron 5000, Deepdive Helmet
 - Mage: Removed Frost Armor from Buffs; it's Passive
 - Mage: Conjure Refreshment Table is the right-click on Conjure Refreshment
 - Stealth: Button is now a standard spell button with tooltips
 - Hunter: Added Camouflage to Stealth button

v6.0.2.15
 - Updated the What's New dialog with the stuff from 6.0.2.14. Oops.

v6.0.2.14
 - More throttling of crazy Blizzard events
 - Mage: Added Ancient Dalaran Portal. Disabled by default.
 - Mage: Removed Mage Armor from buffs; it's a Passive now.
 - Mage: Conjure Food button is disabled on Food and Water buttons by default
 - Food: Button can optionally include Combo Food (Health & Mana)
 - Added a first cut at mining buff potions
 - Hearth: Added Relic of Karabor

v6.0.2.13
 - Added code to throttle out of control Blizzard events
 - Added code to stop bars from popping in briefly while pet battling

v6.0.2.12
 - Milling button was showing "Custom" as its name
 - Garrison button now has data
 - Weird "Food" and "Buttons" addons are no longer added to the Interface->Addons panel
 - Milling (left-click) works again on the Milling button
 - Updated Flasks

v6.0.2.11
 - Milling Button added on Extras bar. Left-click to Mill, Right-Click to use Draenic Mortar
 - Removed Ammo categories since ammo no longer exists
 - Added Oralius' Whispering Crystal to Flasks button
 - Added Garrison button to Extras Bar: Miner's Coffee, Preserved Pick, Salvage, and Iron Traps.

v6.0.2.10
 - Lots of code clean up
 - Added bait to the fishing button
 - Added Worm Supreme and Ephemeral Fishing Pole to fishing button
 - Added Beast Lore to button for Hunters
 - Removed Rotation:Drums
 - In Options window the second "FadeOut" header label now says "General"
 - Fixed bug where newly empty buttons would cover populated ones
 - Mount buttons options: Show Favourites, Show Non-Favourites
 - What's New dialog


v6.0.2.09
 - Added support for button skinning via Masque. ButtonFacade support has been removed.
 - Options to open skinning config from Autobar has been removed; use options provided by Masque directly
 - Mounts button works, but isn't perfect. Some things show that shouldn't.
 - Keybinds menu is cleaned up a bit
 - Added Ashran ports for Mages
 - Added Instant Poison for Combat Rogues, it's an ugly hack to work around a WoW bug
 
 
v6.0.2.08
 - Combo Buff food was missing. It is now on the Combo Food button.

v6.02.07
 - Hunter: Removed Aspect of the Iron Hawk
 - Hunter: Added Aspect of the Fox
 - Removed Mage's Incanter's Flow; it's a Passive but used the same ID as Incanter's Ward which was an Active spell
 - Added Food, Bandage, Potions (Mana, Heal, Rejuv)

v6.0.2.06
 - Updated MuffinLibPTSets
 - Actually *use* the updated food categories

v6.0.2.05:
 - Updates to LibPeriodicTable & MuffinLibPTSets

v6.0.2.04:
 - Grabbed latest version of LibPeriodicTable

v6.0.2.03:
 - Grabbed latest version of MuffinLibPTSets

v6.0.2.02:
 - Removed reference to AceDB-3.0 since it was not used but was referenced.

v6.0.2.01:
 - Fixed bug with Pet button. Still doesn't work, but doesn't throw an error anymore

v6.0.2.00:
 - Updated for Warlords of Draenor pre-patch

v5.4.8.01:
(LibPT)Updated Consumable.Food.Feast
 - Added Bountiful Feast
 - Noodle Carts
 - level for sorting

v5.4.7.5:
 - Embeds MuffinLibPTSets directly since I can't get it to work as I'd like

v5.4.7.4:
 - Openable, Trinket, and Sun Song Ranch buttons should be fixed again
 - Conjure Food is no longer added to the Openable button if you're a rogue (??)

v5.4.7.3:
 - Packaging MuffinLibPTSets

v5.4.7.2:
 - Refresh LibPeriodicTable:
	 - Added Drums of Rage to the Drum Cooldown set
	 - Added Lorewalker's Lodestone, Time-Lost Artifact, Kirin Tor Beacon, and Sunreaver Beacon to Misc.Hearth
	 - Added Volatile Seaforium Blastpack to Misc.Unlock.Seaforium Charges
	 - Added various pet supply bags to Misc.Openable
 - Uses MuffinLibPTSets

v5.4.7.0:
 - Fixed issues with AutoBar disappearing and requiring a /reload

v5.4.1.0:
 - Fixed breakage caused by latest WoW patch

v5.4.0.0:
 - Refresh LibPeriodicTable
 - Improved (hopefully) handling of pet battles/vehicles
 - TOC bump

v5.2.0.0:
 - Refreshed item lists
 - TOC bump
 - Fixed Hunter Aspect button
 - AutoBar will hide when in a vehicle
 - Added code to help find future breakage

v5.1.0.1:
 - A bunch of Openables added to LibPT
 - Flasks should now be up to date

v5.1.0.0:
 - Interface bump
 - Lots of stuff added.
 
v5.0.4.11:
	- Added:
		Brilliant Mana Gem
		Quest: Brazier Torch, Softknuckle Poker, UDED, Transporter Power Cell, Prophetic Ink, Tahret Dynasty Mallet
		Openable: Sack o' Tokens, Pouch o' Tokens
		Fun: Blingotron
		Fishing: Ancient Pandaren Fishing Charm
		Hearth: Wormhole Generator: Pandaria
		Potion: Potion of the Jade Serpent, Potion of the Mountains, Virmen's Bite, Potion of Mogu Power

v5.0.4.10:
 - Hide bars during pet battles
 - For Warlocks, Soul Link is a buff not a shield
 - Added:
		Openable: Hero's Purse
		Fishing Tool:Dragon Fishing Pole
		Quest Items: Orange Painted Turnip, Li Li's Wishing Star, Mudmug's Vial, Zul'Drak Rat

v5.0.4.09:
 - Removed Darkmoon Adventurer's Guide from Misc.Usable.Quest since it is in fact not usable (LibPeriodicTable)
 - Funnel Cakes (from darkmoon faire) show up as food, even though WoW has them misclassified
 - Healing and Mana potions
 - Sunsong Farming button on the Extras bar
 - Removed the Track button, since it hasn't done anything in a long time
 
v5.0.4.08:
 - More foods and drinks added. I'm experimenting with getting data in a way that no longer relies on LibPT.

v5.0.4.07:
 - Massive updates to/of LibPeriodicTable. A lot of missing items should now be there.

v5.0.4.06:
 - Basic MoP Food added to LibPeriodicTable
 

v5.0.4.05:
 - Shaman: Mana Tide Totem is available now
 - Hunter class bar updates
 - Warrior updates
 - Paladin updates.
 - Hunter/Paladin Aura/Aspect button is replaced with Hunter-only Aspect button
 - Added new Poison buttons on the Rogue bar
 - Priests: Removed Vampiric Embrace, added Desperate Prayer to ER
 - DeathKnights have pets
 - Fishing on the Extras bar works again
 - Basic Monk support

v5.0.4.04:
 - Try to nicely deprecate removed button classes
 
v5.0.4.03:
 - Possible fix for Shaman Water Totems not showing (I can't test it)
 - Updated trinket list with a new experimental process (hopefully it works)
 - Updated LibPeriodicTable
 - Removed LibBabbleZone-3.0 and AceDebug-2.0
 - Removed handling of Burning Crusade instance-only items
 - Removed popup dialogs when right-clicking on bars
 - You should delete the original AutoBar folder before upgrading since some files were removed
 